

Phurikorn Thongyoi

062-597-6969 · (10/01/2002)

phurikornpt@gmail.com · @github.com/phurikornpt 118 Soi Chan 2, Chan Road, Thung Wat Don Sathon District Bangkok 10120

web-profile: nextjs-personal-web-ten.vercel.app

SUMMARY

Bachelor of Engineering Program in Electronics Engineering Technology (Computer) at King Mongkut's University of Technology North Bangkok in 2024. I have internship experience as a Backend Developer for 4 months, which has sparked my interest in this field. Therefore, I am interested in positions such as Backend Developer, Software Engineer, and Fullstack Developer.

SKILL

- Backend
 - Javascript/Typescript
 - Python, C/C++
 - Node.js / Express.js
 - Nest.js
 - PostgreSQL, MongoDB
 - Prisma, TypeORM
 - Docker

- Fontend
 - HTML / CSS
 - React / Next.js
 - Mui , tailwind
- CMS
 - PayloadCMS

- Tool
 - Postman
 - Git/Github
 - Jira , MiroNotion
- Languages
 - Thai (Native)
 - English (B1)

EXPERIENCE

Develop a website for managing the Shabu Buffet restaurant | January 2022

- Develop a website and design a database for internal data management within the restaurant.
- Tool: Nodejs/Express.js, EJS, Access

Assisting with university research: Developing AMR Robot | May 2022 - January 2023

- Develop a website to control robot operations, create maps, generate movement plans, and display realtime robot positions
- Tool: Ubuntu 18.04, Nodejs/Express.js, EJS, Websocket, ROS

Assisting with university research: Rice donates machine | September 2023

- Develop a website and design a database for a dashboard web application to display user data regarding rice donation machine usage
- Tool: PHP, Mysql, Hostinger

Backend Developer Internship at Codemonday Company | November 2023 - April 2024

- Responsible for developing APIs and designing the database schema for assigned modules.
- Develop a CMS system for content and data management for user accessibility.
- Design and develop email templates for the mail-sending system.
- Coordinate with frontend designers project manager and QA personnel in system development.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Technology 2020 - 2024

Bachelor of Engineering Program in Electronics EngineeringTechnology (Computer) King Mongkut's University of Technology North Bangkok **GPAX 3.22**

EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

Robot Competition Event | 2022

Second Place Winner: Robot CARC Competition

Training Speaker | 2021 - 2023

Being a training speaker in STEM even, teaching programming in C/C++ for robot control, at King Mongkut's University of Technology North Bangkok.

Tutor | 2021 - Present

Tutor in programming:

- Python
- Arduino / Robotics